helixstudios.net 2019-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Helix Studios

Helix, Inc., including its wholly owned (directly and indirectly) subsidiaries (hereinafter “Helix”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the personal information of our customers, employees and third parties. 

This Privacy Notice highlights how Helix uses the information collected through its websites, apps, and services. 

## 1\. Information We Collect

###  1.1 Summary 

Helix collects many kinds of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. We collect information when you register, sign in and use our sites and services. We also may get information from other companies. We collect this information in a variety of ways, including from web forms, technologies like cookies, web logging and software on your computer or other device. 

We use information submitted through our websites or collected through email or hard copy surveys to analyze the characteristics of our customers and improve our services. 

If you request information about Helix products and services, we will collect your name, email address, phone number, and additional personal information. We use this information to contact you about your request, and to follow up with you about the products and services in which you have expressed an interest. We will also send information to you regarding upcoming Helix events, releases, and relevant privacy related news and alerts. You may unsubscribe from these communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided in the email. 

Helix receives and processes information (in paper and electronic form) in accordance with its clients’ instructions for the purpose of providing services to its customers. At Helix, we recognize the importance of privacy to our customers and we strive to safeguard any personal information we receive and may need to use in support of our customers. 

We respect each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information we receive directly from you only in the ways disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This policy does not apply to practices that Helix does not own or control, or to individuals that Helix does not employ or manage. 

In addition, we provide appropriate employee training (and discipline) and have internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of our compliance with Privacy Principles. 

###  1.2 Full Text 

Helix collects many kinds of information in order to operate effectively and provide you the best products, services and experiences we can. Some of this information you provide directly to us. Some of it we get by observing how you interact with our products and services. Some of it is available from other sources that we may combine with the data we collect directly. Regardless of the source, we believe it's important to treat that information with care and to help you maintain your privacy. 

## What we collect:

\- Registration   
When you sign up to use our sites or services you may be required to provide information about yourself, such as your name, birthdate, e-mail and postal address and postal code. 

\- Signing in   
To access some Helix services, you will need to sign in with a user name and password, which we refer to as your user account. 

\- Using our sites and services   
We collect information that tells us how you interact with our services, including the browser you're using, your IP address, location, cookies or other unique IDs, the pages you visit and features you use. 

\- Data from other sources - We may get additional information about you, such as demographic data we purchase from other companies. 

## How we collect:

We use a number of methods and technologies to gather information about how you use our sites and services, such as: 

\- Web forms, such as when you type information into a registration form or type a search query into a search box. 

\- Technologies like cookies and web beacons (Please visit Section 2 of this Privacy Policy page to learn more about these technologies). 

\- Web logging, which enables us to collect the standard information your browser sends to every web site you visit - such as your IP address, browser type and language, and the site you came from - as well as the pages you visit and the links you click while using our sites and services. 

\- Software installed on your computer or other device, which may send back information needed to operate, update or improve that software. 

## Customer Data:

Helix receives and processes information (in paper and electronic form) in accordance with its clients’ instructions for the purpose of providing services to its customers. At Helix, we recognize the importance of privacy to our customers and we strive to safeguard any personal information we receive and may need to use in support of our customers. 

Helix Customer Information 

Customer Information is information we collect from you when you purchase and contract with us to provide services or technology solutions. We will ask you to provide the following information: 

\- Email address; 

\- Phone number; 

\- Personal information, including name, address, billing information (debit or credit card number); 

This is information is stored on Helix’s systems, and is used to provide services in accordance with the applicable terms and conditions. 

## 2\. Cookies & Similar Technologies

###  2.1 Summary 

Most Helix web sites use "cookies," small pieces of data that can be read by a web server in the same domain that put the cookie on your hard drive. We may use cookies to help us retrieve your preferences and settings; help with sign-in; to combat fraud; and analyze site operations. 

We also use web beacons to help deliver cookies and compile analytics. These may include third-party web beacons, which are prohibited from collecting your personal information. 

You have a variety of tools to control cookies and similar technologies, including: 

\- Browser controls to block and delete cookies; and 

\- Controls from some analytics providers to opt out of data collection in web beacons. 

###  2.2 Full text 

####  2.2.1 Our Use of Cookies 

Most Helix web sites use “cookies,” which are small pieces of data sent to your browser by a web server. Upon subsequent requests, your browser will send the cookie data to the same web server, or other web servers in the same domain, when accessing the web site. Cookies contain data that can be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. That data often consists of a string of numbers and letters that uniquely identifies your computer but may contain other information as well. Here is an example of a unique ID number stored in a cookie that Helix might place on your device when you visit one of our web sites: 9ha56er983130kmrtsx6jjabseniu65sjdjnnu9 

We may use cookies for: 

\- Sign-in and Authentication   
When you sign in to a site or service using your account on an Helix web site, we store a unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. This is commonly referred to as a “session cookie”. We also use cookies to improve the sign-in experience. For example, your user name may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your user name to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used. 

\- Site Analytics   
We may use cookies to count the number of unique visitors to a web page or service or to develop other aggregate statistics about the operations of our sites and services. These analytics help us operate and improve the performance of these sites and services. 

In addition to the cookies Helix may set when you visit our web sites, third parties may also set certain cookies on your device when you visit Helix sites. In some cases, that is because we have hired the third party to provide certain services on our behalf, such as site analytics. In other cases, it is because our web pages contain content or ads from third parties, such as videos, news content or ads delivered by other ad networks. Because your browser connects to those third parties’ web servers to retrieve that content, those third parties are able to set or read their own cookies on your device and may collect information about your online activities across websites or online services. 

####  2.2.2 How to Control Cookies 

\- Browser Controls to Block Cookies.   
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to block cookies. Instructions for blocking cookies in different browsers are usually available at each browser’s privacy statement or in their help files or settings pages.   
Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Helix sites and services that depend on cookies. 

\- Browser Controls to Delete Cookies   
If you accept cookies, you can delete them later. Instructions for deleting cookies in different browsers are usually available at each browser’s privacy statement or in their help files or settings pages.   
Please be aware that if you choose to delete cookies, any settings and preferences controlled by those cookies will be deleted and may need to be recreated. 

\- Browser Controls for “Do Not Track” and Tracking Protection   
Some newer browsers have incorporated “Do Not Track” features. Most of these features, when turned on, send a signal or preference to the web sites you visit indicating that you do not wish to be tracked. Those sites (or the third party content on those sites) may continue to engage in activities you might view as tracking even though you have expressed this preference, depending on the sites’ privacy practices. Because there is not yet a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, Helix does not currently respond to the browser DNT signals on its own websites or online services, or on third-party websites or online services where Helix provides content or is otherwise able to collect information. 

####  2.2.3 Our Use of Web Beacons 

Helix web pages may contain electronic images known as web beacons - sometimes called single pixel gifs - that may be used to help deliver cookies on our sites, let us count users who have visited those pages and deliver co-branded services. We may include web beacons in our promotional e-mail messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. 

Finally, Helix sites may contain web beacons from third parties to help us compile aggregated statistics regarding the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other web site operations. These web beacons may allow the third parties to set or read a cookie on your computer. These companies may collect information about your online activities across websites or online servers, however, we prohibit third parties from using web beacons on our sites to collect or access your personal information. You may be able to opt out from data collection or use by these third-party analytics companies by opting out on their respective web sites. 

####  2.2.4 Other Similar Technologies 

In addition to standard cookies and web beacons, web sites can use other technologies to store and read data files on your computer. This may be done to maintain your preferences or to improve speed and performance by storing certain files locally. But, like standard cookies, it can also be used to store a unique identifier for your computer, which can then be used to track behavior. 

\- Local Shared Objects or "Flash cookies"   
Web sites that use Adobe Flash technologies may use Local Shared Objects or "Flash cookies" to store data on your computer. Note that the ability to clear Flash cookies may or may not be controlled by your browser setting for standard cookies as that may vary by browser. To manage or block Flash cookies, go to the appropriate settings page, currently to be found at http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html. 

\- Silverlight Application Storage   
Web sites or applications that use Microsoft Silverlight technology also have the ability to store data by using Silverlight Application Storage. To learn how to manage or block such storage, visit the Silverlight Privacy Statement. 

## 3\. How We Use Your Personal Information

###  3.1 Summary 

Helix uses the information we collect to operate, improve and personalize the products and services we offer. 

Customer Information will be used to provide the services and access to technology solutions you have purchased and the corresponding support. 

We also may use the information to communicate with you, for example, informing you about your account and security updates. 

And we may use the information to help make the ads you see on our ad-supported services more relevant. 

###  3.2 Full text 

Helix uses the information we collect to operate, improve and personalize the products and services we offer. Information collected through one Helix service may be combined with information collected through other Helix services to give you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with us. We may also supplement this with information from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies to help us derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area. 

We also may use the information to communicate with you, for example, informing you when a subscription is ending, letting you know when updates are available or letting you know when you need to take action to keep your account active. We may also use the information, if the law allows it or if we have your express permission to do so, to contact you for sales or marketing purposes. 

We will use your Customer Information to: 

\- Provide the services and premium access you have purchased; 

\- Renew subscription-based services; 

\- Provide customer support. While providing you with customer support we may also gather additional information from you to investigate technical issues, and respond to your support questions; 

\- Communicate regularly with you about your use of the software and service, Helix events and other industry or privacy-related news, and other Helix services we believe may be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving emails regarding Helix events and other Helix services by clicking unsubscribe link provided in the email. You will continue to receive notices regarding Helix software and technical services you purchased, and privacy-related updates such as notification of new or changes to existing privacy regulations 

## 4\. Reasons We Share Your Personal Information 

###  4.1 Summary 

Except as described in this privacy statement, we won’t disclose your personal information to a third party without your consent. 

Please see Other Important Privacy Information for details about when we may disclose information, including with Helix affiliates and vendors; when required by law or to respond to legal process; to combat fraud or protect our interest; or to protect lives. 

###  4.2 Full text 

Except as described in this privacy statement, we won’t disclose your personal information to a third party without your consent. Contexts and situations where we may disclose your personal data without your consent are: 

\- Within Helix affiliates and subsidiaries 

\- As part of a merger or sale of a business 

\- With vendors and agents of Helix 

\- When required by law or to respond to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement or other government agencies or other public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements 

\- When required to combat fraud or protect our interests 

\- To protect life and safety 

Please also refer to section 11.2.2 to learn more about why and with whom we share or disclose personal information. 

## 5\. Accessing Your Personal Information

###  5.1 Summary 

Some Helix services may give you the ability to view or edit your personal information online. To help prevent others from viewing your personal information, you first might be required to sign in. How you can access your personal information will depend on which sites or services you have used. 

###  5.2 Full text 

Some Helix services may give you the ability to view or edit your personal information online. To help prevent your personal information from being viewed by others, you first will be required to sign in. The method(s) for accessing your personal information will depend on which sites or services you have used. 

Each Helix web site may provide you with links to access, correct or delete your personal data. You can also contact Helix by using a provided contact form on the web site or by contacting the office of the General Counsel (legal at helixstudios dot com). We will respond to requests to access or delete your personal information within 30 days. 

Accessing and Updating your Personal Information 

To review and update your personally identifying information to ensure it is accurate, contact us vial email: privacy at Helix dot com 

Helix will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable access to any of your personal information we maintain within 30 days of your access request. We provide this access so you can review, make corrections, or request deletion of your data. If we cannot honor your request within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will be able to provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to this information, we will explain why we cannot do so. 

## 6\. Under Age Internet Users

###  6.1 Full Text 

When a Helix site or service collects age information, it will block users under 18. Users under age 18, or the legal age to view adult entertainment in your jurisdiction, whichever is higher, are not allowed to view or access any Helix website. 

## 7\. Communication Preferences

###  7.1 Summary 

You can stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from Helix sites and services by following the specific instructions in the e-mail you receive. Depending on the respective service, you may also have the option of proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional e-mail and materials for particular Helix sites or services. 

###  7.2 Full text 

If you receive promotional e-mails from us and would like to stop getting them in the future, you can do so by following the directions in that message. 

Depending on the respective service, you may also have the option of proactively making choices about the receipt of promotional e-mail or other promotional materials from particular Helix sites or services by visiting and signing into the following pages: 

These choices do not apply to the receipt of mandatory service communications that are considered part of certain Helix services, which you may receive periodically unless you cancel the service. 

## 8\. International Users - Applicable Law

###  8.1 Summary 

Your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other countries. Helix may transfer information to our corporate affiliates, service providers, and other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These partners provide us with services globally, including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales, marketing, data analysis, research and surveys. 

###  8.2 Full text 

Please note that the personal information you submit to us may be transferred to the United States and other countries to be processed by us in order to provide this Web Site, our technology solutions and services to you or for such other purposes as set forth in this Policy. Helix may transfer information to our corporate affiliates, service providers, and other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These partners provide us with services globally, including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales, marketing, data analysis, research and surveys. 

## 9\. Support Data

### 9.1 Summary

Support Data is the information we collect when you submit a support request or run an automated troubleshooter, including information about hardware, software, and other details related to the support incident, such as: contact or authentication information, chat session personalization, information about the condition of the machine and the application from when the fault occurred and during diagnostics, system and registry data about software installations and hardware configurations, and error-tracking files. We use Support Data as described in this privacy statement, and additionally use it to resolve your support incident and for training purposes. 

###  9.2 Full text 

Support Data is the information we collect when you submit a support request or run an automated troubleshooter, including information about hardware, software, and other details related to the support incident, such as: contact or authentication information, chat session personalization, information about the condition of the machine and the application from when the fault occurred and during diagnostics, system and registry data about software installations and hardware configurations, and error- tracking files. We use Support Data as described in this privacy statement, and additionally use it to resolve your support incident and for training purposes. 

Support may be provided through phone, e-mail, or online chat. Phone conversations or online chat sessions with support professionals may be recorded and/or monitored. 

Following a support incident, we may send you a survey about your experience and offerings. You must opt-out of support surveys separately from other communications provided by Helix, by contacting Support or through the e-mail footer. 

To review and edit your personal information collected through our support services, please contact us by using our Web form or email address provided above. 

## 10\. Payment Data

###  10.1 Summary 

Payment Data is the information that you provide when you make purchases. This may include your payment instrument number (e.g., credit card, bank account number), your name and billing address, and the security code associated with your payment instrument (e.g., the CSV or CVV). This section provides additional information regarding the collection and use of your payment information. 

###  10.2 Full text 

Payment Data is the information that you provide when you make purchases. This may include your payment instrument number (e.g., credit card, bank account number), your name and billing address, and the security code associated with your payment instrument (e.g., the CSV or CVV). This section provides additional information regarding the collection and use of your payment information. 

Payment Data is used to complete your transaction, as well as for the detection and prevention of fraud. In support of these uses, Helix may share your Payment Data with banks and other entities that process payment transactions or other financial services, and for fraud prevention and credit risk reduction. 

When you provide Payment Data to us, we may store that data to help you complete future transactions. 

You may remove the payment instrument information associated with your organizational account by contacting us. After you close your account or remove a payment instrument, however, Helix may retain your payment instrument data for as long as reasonably necessary to complete your existing transaction, to comply with Helix’s legal and reporting requirements, and for the detection and prevention of fraud. 

## 11\. Other Important Privacy Information

###  11.1 Summary 

Learn more about 

\- Why and with whom we share or disclose personal information 

\- Protecting the security of personal information 

\- Where we store and process information 

\- Changes to our privacy statements 

\- How to Contact Us 

###  11.2 Full text 

Below you will find additional privacy information you may find important. Much of this describes practices that are common across the entertainment industry, but we want make sure you are aware of them. Please keep in mind that this information is not a complete description of our practices - this is all in addition to the other, more specific information contained elsewhere in this privacy statement. 

####  11.2.1 On this page: 

\- Sharing or Disclosing Personal Information 

\- Protecting the Security of Personal Information 

\- Where Information is Stored and Processed 

\- Changes to Our Privacy Statements 

\- How to Contact Us 

####  11.2.2 Sharing or Disclosing Personal Information 

Helix transfers information to our corporate affiliates, service providers, and other partners who process it for us, based on our instructions, and in compliance with this policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. These partners provide us with services globally, including for customer support, information technology, payments, sales, marketing, data analysis, research and surveys. In addition to any sharing described above in this privacy statement, Helix may share or disclose personal information: 

\- With other Helix controlled subsidiaries and affiliates. 

\- As part of a corporate transaction such as a merger or sale of assets. 

\- With vendors or agents. Specifically, we may share it with companies we've hired to provide services on our behalf. Examples of these services include analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and processing credit card payments. When we share information with these other companies to provide services for us, they are not allowed to use it for any other purpose and must keep it confidential. 

We also may share or disclose personal information, including the content of your communications: 

\- To comply with the law or respond to legal process or lawful requests, including from law enforcement and government agencies or other public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

\- To protect the rights or property of Helix or our customers, including enforcing the terms governing your use of the services. 

\- To act on a good faith belief that access or disclosure is necessary to protect the personal safety of Helix employees, customers or the public. 

Please note that our sites may include links to third-party sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Helix. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by the privacy statements on those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy statement of any site you visit. 

####  11.2.3 Protecting the Security of Personal Information 

Helix is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems that have limited access and are in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Transport Layer Security (TLS) or Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocols. 

If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share it. If you are sharing a computer, you should always log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

####  11.2.4 Where Information is Stored and Processed 

Personal information collected on Helix sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where Helix or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. We take steps to ensure that the data we collect under this privacy statement is processed according to the provisions of this statement and the requirements of applicable law wherever the data is located. 

Helix may retain your personal information for a variety of reasons, such as to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, and as long as necessary to provide services. To learn how to access your personal information, visit Accessing Your Information. 

####  11.2.5 Changes to Our Privacy Statements 

We will occasionally update our privacy statements to reflect customer feedback and changes in our services. When we post changes to a statement, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the statement. If there are material changes to the statement or in how Helix will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes before they take effect or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review the privacy statements for the products and services you use to learn how Helix is protecting your information. 

####  11.2.6 How to Contact Us 

\- If you have a technical or general support question, please visit [ https://www.helixstudios.net/preview/custsvc.php ](https://www.helixstudios.net/preview/custsvc.php) ? 

to learn more about Helix Support offerings. 

\- If you have a general privacy question, or a question with regards to this Privacy Policy, please contact Helix’s Office of the General Counsel: legal at helixstudios dot com 

Accessing and Updating your Personal Information 

\- To review and update your personally identifying information to ensure it is accurate, contact us vial email: privacy at HelixStudios dot com 

\- Helix will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide you reasonable access to any of your personal information we maintain within 30 days of your access request. We provide this access so you can review, make corrections, or request deletion of your data. If we cannot honor your request within the 30-day period, we will tell you when we will be able to provide access. In the unlikely event that we cannot provide you access to this information, we will explain why we cannot do so. 

* * *

Helix, Inc., including its wholly owned (directly and indirectly) subsidiaries (hereinafter “Helix”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of the personal information of our customers, employees and third parties. Helix sites include HelixStudios.com, HelixStudios.net, 8teenboy.com, GuysHangOut.com, GuysBang.com, SpankthisHookups.com, Spankthis.com and MankindVideo.com.
